killscreen.com 2019-05-13

# Privacy Policy - Kill Screen

**Privacy Policy**

The web site Killscreendaily.com (“Site”) is a website of Kill Screen Media, Inc. (“Kill Screen”) who is committed to protecting the privacy of information you provide to this site. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Site and governs collection and usage of personal data through this Site. This Statement of Privacy does not apply to other Kill Screen sites, products, or services.

By using this Site, you consent to the collection and use of the information and data as described here. If we decide to change this privacy policy, we will post the changes on this page so that you will always know what information we collect, and how we use it.

**Collection and Use of Personal Data:**  
On the Site, we only store personal information relating to you with your permission. You may choose to reveal information to us if, for example, you register for a service, enter a contest or complete a survey. If you choose to register for an activity on the Site, you may be asked for your formal consent regarding collection and usage of your personally identifiable information. Unless otherwise stated when you register, the personal information collected on this Site will be used to operate the Site and to provide the service(s) or carry out the transaction(s) you have requested or authorized.

Once shared, Kill Screen will only use your personal information in accordance with the purpose for which it was originally shared.

Third parties such as Federated Media Publishing who assist Kill Screen in the management of the Site may access and collect information on behalf of Kill Screen through the Site, but they are not allowed to use this data for their own business purposes separate from their relationship with Kill Screen. We will only share your personal data with these third parties according to applicable data protection laws or with your express permission. This data is used by these third parties solely for the purposes described under this Privacy Statement.

Kill Screen will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so or in line with applicable laws.

**Advertising:  
**First Party Ad Serving  This website’s ads are served by Google’s DoubleClick. Kill Screen uses only first party data (collected during your current and recent visits) about your visits to this site to serve ads to you. We will not share your first party data with any other third parties and is only used for proprietary ad delivery and ad reporting.

Third Party Advertising and Cookies  Kill Screen works with third party advertising partners who may distribute cookies to users in advertisements that are provided to us from time to time. Kill Screen has no access to or control over these third party cookies.

Opt-out  In support of your privacy, you can use the following links to opt-out of cookies provided by both our first party ad server and many third party advertising partners who may be engaging in online behavioral advertising:

First Party Opt-out  Please visit this link to opt-out of cookies from our first party ad serving vendor, Google:

<http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/>

Third Party and Online Behavioral Advertising Opt-out  Please visit this link to opt-out of cookies from over 50+ major third party behavioral advertising providers:

<http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>

**Links to Other Sites:  
**This site contains links to other sites. Kill Screen is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of third party web sites you may access through the Site.

**Inquiries:**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement please contact us at [info@killscreendaily.com](mailto:info@killscreenmagazine.com).

* * *
